JEAN HAMPTON

jeanhampton205@gmail.com | 406-475-1015 | Helena, MT 59601

y
ÿ

Hardworking and motivated with 10 years of working experience. Solid history of balancing team performance, customer service targets and business objectives. Dedicated to working closely with front-line employees to maximize productivity and optimize procedures. Decisive leader with good planning and organizational skills. Has excellent communication skills and a strong ability to lead.

Skills -

- Issue resolution
- POS systems
- Content generation
- Customer assistance

- Trained in Brackets
- Problem resolution
- Administrative support

Experience -

Administrative Assistant | Freeman & MacLean - Helena, MT | 09/2020 - Current

- Oversaw office inventory by restocking supplies and submitting purchase orders.
- Supported office needs including taking messages, scanning documents and routing business correspondence.
- Monitored office supply use and stock levels, placing replenishment orders as needed.
- Organized and maintained filing and document management systems by coordinating, archiving and purging files.

Cashier | Bullman's Wood Fired Pizza - Helena, MT | 05/2014 - Current

- Properly verified customer identification for alcohol or tobacco purchases.
- Resolved issues with cash registers, card scanners and printers.
- Maintained high productivity by efficiently processing cash, credit, debit and voucher program payments for customers.
- Completed daily recovery tasks to keep areas clean and neat for maximum efficiency.
- Processed customer payments quickly and returned exact change and receipts.
- Trained new team members in cash register operation, stock procedures and customer service.
- Resolved issues regarding customer complaints and escalated worsening concerns to manager for remediation.
- Worked closely with front-end staff to assist customers and maintain satisfaction levels.
- Educated guests on daily specials and appetizers, entrees, desserts and other menu items.
- Prepared salads, appetizers and set up garnish stations to assist kitchen staff.
- Checked on guests to verify satisfaction with meals and suggested additional items to increase restaurant sales.
- Communicated with kitchen staff frequently to stay up-to-date on supply availability and potential customer wait times.
- Applied safe food handling and optimal cleaning strategies to protect customers from foodborne illness and maintain proper sanitation.
- Minimized customer wait times by efficiently taking and filling large volume of orders each day.

- Facilitated communication through effective management of incoming correspondences, including phone calls, emails and letters.
- Wrote and uploaded quality posts for client's various social media pages, improving overall traffic.
- Kept respective team leads informed of rising issues and trends surfacing on social media.
- Created focused social media strategy resulting in an increase in website traffic from social media posts.
- Participated in brainstorming sessions to discuss ideas and develop business campaigns.
- Analyzed and monitored social media engagement.

Daycare Assistant | Little Flower Infant Care - Helena, MT | 08/2018 - 07/2019

- Helped prepare meals, snacks and refreshments for children, accounting for individual dietary needs and restrictions.
- Secured indoor and outdoor premises to protect children under care.
- Managed crafts and other hands-on activities to engage kids and promote development.
- Led children in tidying up, handwashing and other tasks to teach responsibility.
- Attended to lunch periods to help children open food packages and monitor activities
- Enforced rules to teach manners and maintain safe environment.
- Delivered direct, supervised care to groups of children between ages 8 months and 5 years old.
- Cared for up to 13 children ranging in age from 8 months to 5 years old.
- Applied patience and expertise to maintain group discipline.

Education and Training -

Carroll College | Helena, MT | Expected in 05/2021

Bachelor of Arts: Business Marketing And Management